Choirul Afandi

WEB DEVELOPER

Surabaya | +62 83830956015 | productive.afandi@gmail.com

afandiweb.com

Summary

Hi, i'm Afandi. A passionate and fast learner PHP Developer with over 4+ years experience from Surabaya, Indonesia.

I have developed many website for famous brand in Indonesia.

I'm specialized on developement diferent types of web projects: company profile, web applications, facebook application, e-commerce and so on. My very primary attention is to develop website in professional way and with great quality.

Professional experience

Web Developer

Onesoft.id

Consume And Produce API for travel agent system and make program B2B for Travel.

Web Developer

January 2017 - Oktober 2017

Oktober 2017 - Now

Pilarmedia Indonesia

Creating CRM, Dashboard management for PJB (Pembangkit Jawa Bali), and creating Fleet Management system.

Web Developer

February 2016 - December 2016

PT. Alun Alun Nusantara

Creating website B2B Marketplace

Web Developer

May 2013 - February 2016

PT. Dhezign Online Solution

As a Web Programmer. Developed website for many famous brand in Indonesia using wordpress and native. Integrating API for Shoop! Ecommerce Mobile Apps. Developed ecommerce platform that used by Indosat (now Indosat Ooredoo) for http://cipika.co.id.

Education

Software Engineering major

2010 - 2013

Vocational High School 2, Surabaya

Software Engineering major. Active in school organization and representing school in national software competition. In this High School I began to love on web development. The education was basic web development like HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP. I'm here learn litle about Java and OOP.



Skills

PHP

HTML/CSS

MySQL

OOP

MVC